Silva! Do it now!
[Silva grunts]
[explosion]
[theme music playing]
FAKE x AND x PSYCHE
[thunder clapping]
[indistinct chatter]
[man 1] Hey! What the hell is going on?
[man 2] It came from below
There was a huge explosion underneath us.
I'm through with waiting!
I’m gonna go see for myself!
[Bean] Everyone, calm down.
Moments ago, we were able to get
in touch with the Ten Dons.
They wish to speak to you directly
through a live video feed.
The auction will proceed as planned,
so try to remain calm.
Please enter the auction hall
on the tenth floor.
[executive 1] I'll be fine.
This is on the tenth floor.
I'll be safe as long
as I don't go downstairs.
[executive 2] It'll be alright.
Her fortunes are 100 percent accurate.
[executive 3] As long as you heed
the warning, her fortunes won’t come true.
Nothing to worry about.
[electricity surging]
Hey. How is everybody doing?
First, I apologize for being
out of touch. Sorry.
Things got a little bit messy there,
but everything is fine now.
The leader of the infamous Phantom Troupe
has been dealt with.
[indistinct chatter]
It's only a matter of time
before we get to the rest of them.
So leave all the hunting
to the professionals
and enjoy the rest of your auction.
[audience cheering]
Tonight is a special occasion,
so we’ll be watching live.
And of course, we look forward
to seeing some serious bidding.
You heard it for yourselves, gentlemen.
The Ten Dons will be watching
a live feed of the proceedings.
Please concentrate on the auction.
[fly buzzing]
[thunder crashing]
[phone ringing]
That you, Illumi?
[Illumi] Yeah. Where's my client?
[Silva] He's here.
[Zeno groaning]
Oh. Were you two just fighting?
So, is he still alive?
Just in the nick of time.
Good. Give him a message for me.
We've disposed of the Ten Dons.
And tell him to wire the money
to the account. He knows the one.
Up we go. Well, what a surprise.
Seems we both get to live another day.
[Chrollo] But your mission?
[Zeno]
The Ten Dons were our clients, you see.
And so now that they’ve all been
disposed of, things have changed.
You are no longer our target.
Huh. I see.
You won't get another chance like this.
Perhaps. But you don’t really think
we’re in this business
for the fun of it, do you?
It’s not as if we take any pleasure
in killing.
And I certainly don’t want to work
or die for nothing.
I was the one who commissioned Illumi
to assassinate the Ten Dons.
Did you know that?
Of course, I did. But that is irrelevant.
Makes no difference.
We simply do the job we're hired to do
and nothing more.
I understand.
-So, can I ask you something?
-[Zeno grunts]
If we were to fight, just the two of us,
which of us would win?
Hmm. I would.
There's no question about it.
Though it would be
a different story altogether
if you were actually trying to kill me.
Damn insolent brat.
[Chrollo] So he knew?
[sighs]
[thudding]
I'm so beat!
I’ve no chance
of stealing their abilities.
[Melody] So, you want us to wait
at Hospital L?
[Kurapika] Yes, it's more dangerous here
than we thought.
We'll send her over by ambulance
in a short while.
[doctor] She's just unconscious,
so you shouldn't have to worry.
But she'll certainly be a lot safer
at the hospital than she is here.
Make the preparations.
[Franklin] Looks like you had fun, boss.
You doing okay?
[Chrollo] Yeah. Just a little tired,
that’s all.
You did go up against the Zoldyck family.
I wish I’d been there to see.
Watching how those two fought you
would have been very informative.
[Feitan]
Fighting would be more fun than watching.
Kortopi, are we all ready
to do the next step?
Of course. I can't make living copies,
just ones that don't move.
[Chrollo] Good enough.
We'll stick to the plan.
Also...
[sighs] Don't touch the ambulance
that's carrying the girl.
You really think that we'll be safe
on the trip over?
If they were planning
to attack the ambulance,
they would've done so on its way here.
Stray bullets shouldn't be a concern
anymore, either.
[auctioneer] It's the moment
you've been waiting for!
Get ready, because this auction
is about to begin!
[audience applauding]
If you would,
please allow me to introduce
the first item of the evening!
[Bean sighs] I was getting worried there
for a moment.
But all's well that ends well.
None of the leaders were hurt.
So, at least there's that.
We did alright.
Hmm?
Thank you.
-Huh?
-[Hisoka snickers]
Coming up next,
another splendid item for you!
A solid gold execution sword,
direct from the Yul National Treasury!
[audience exclaiming]
Bidding starts at 20 million!
-[man 1] 40 million!
-[man 2] 50!
[auctioneer] I hear 50 million Jenny.
Thank you, sir.
[man 3] One hundred million!
I guess I can put him on autopilot. There.
Next, we have a Celadon porcelain vase
from the Lai Dynasty.
It’s still completely intact,
and is, without a doubt, the very last
of its kind in the entire world.
Okay, so where’s the Celadon vase? Um…
Here it is.
Kortopi, this one is next.
Here, I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
[audience exclaiming]
[auctioneer]
And here’s the Celadon vase now!
Let's start the bidding off
at 100 million!
-[man 1] 200 million!
-[man 2] 330!
[man 3] 380!
[sirens wailing]
[guard] Hey, you there.
Aren't you gonna participate
in the auction?
What are you talking about?
The leader of the Phantom Troupe
was killed.
-[gasping]
-[guard 2] Moving ahead as planned.
But that's impossible.
It can't be.
[guard] They're hunting down
the stragglers now.
[guard 2]
They don't call 'em pros for nothing.
[Zenji chuckling]
While your useless ass was busy
wasting time with the ambulance,
it looks like the Zoldycks
actually stepped up and got the job done.
And since there's no real need
for you any longer,
why don't you just run along and suck up
to your fortuneteller girl?
Head over to the hospital,
maybe the hotel, eh?
Or even better, how about you go
and lick the boots
of that old fraud who's just
as useless as you?
Sound good? [yelps]
[Kurapika] I won't believe it
until I see it with my own eyes.
[man 1] This is the leader?
He's young.
Too young to be messing with us.
[man 2]
Hey, don't damage him from the neck up.
We're gonna put his face on the Internet.
[man 3] We found the other members!
[man 4] Right, I'm on my way.
Five bodies, total?
Try to identify them.
DNA, teeth, fingerprints.
Check all the databases.
And whatever you do,
don't touch their heads.
[man 5] Once we know who they are,
we'll kill their relatives,
their lovers, everyone!
Make sure the whole world knows
that this is what happens
when you screw with us like this.
[Kurapika grunting]
[panting]
[auctioneer] Alright, everyone.
This is it!
It's time for our very last item
of the night!
One of the seven most beautiful colors
in the world, the Scarlet Eyes!
[audience exclaiming]
[auctioneer]
Now that the Kurta Clan's extinct,
only 36 pairs will ever exist.
This particular pair exhibits
an exceptionally brilliant scarlet.
So, let's start the bidding
at 100 million!
-[man 1] 110 million!
-[dialing]
[man 2] 120!
[man 3] 130!
-[man 1] 150!
-[call connects]
-[Kurapika] Boss?
-A-hundred-seventy!
-[Kurapika] It's Kurapika.
-[bidding continues]
[Kurapika] I apologize.
I predicted incorrectly.
The leader of the Spiders is dead
and the auction is proceeding
as scheduled.
[Nostrade] What?
[Kurapika] The Scarlet Eyes
are being auctioned as we speak.
-Should I bid?
-Of course! You must win them.
Is there a limit, sir?
No! Bid whatever it takes to win them.
Yes, sir. I understand.
-[man 4] 300!
-I hear 300 million Jenny!
Do I have any other bids out there?
Anyone at all?
-[Kurapika] 350!
-[gasps]
[man 1] 360!
[man 2] 370!
[man 3] 390!
Five hundred!
[Zenji] One billion.
[gasping]
[snickering]
[Nostrade] 2.9 billion?
[Kurapika] Yes, sir. That's right.
Unfortunately, I got into a bidding war
with the bald man
from the assassin's meeting.
Zenji, huh? Damn it.
[Nostrade] I didn't expect him
to spend this much.
Curse that loathsome pig.
But no matter.
This means more money for the community,
which will only serve to bolster
my prestige.
As long as I have Neon's fortunetelling,
I can make it back.
Fine. It won't be a problem.
You did well, so thank you.
That's right.
This is just an investment
in my journey to the top.
In order to succeed, it's imperative
that I keep Neon happy.
She's my secret weapon.
Now and forever.
As long as I have her... [snickering]
I'll have all the money I could ever want.
[auctioneer]
You're from the Nostrade Family?
Congratulations on your winning bid.
Please confirm that this is your item.
[Kurapika] Yeah.
[Zenji] You bastard.
Did you really think
you could get away from me?
Hold it! Or I'll blow your head off!
Move.
You little...
[grunting]
Don't tempt me right now.
I don’t care who I lash out at.
[whimpering]
[Kurapika] It might as well be you.
[groaning]
[panting]
Who in the hell... is that kid?
[panting continues]
[Leorio and Zepile laughing]
[Leorio] Let the good times roll!
How's about another?
[Killua] Really?
We were captured and these two
were sitting here drinking?
Hey! You're back, huh?
Join the party!
Come on, have a drink with us.
Idiot. We’re not old enough
to drink alcohol!
And I'm pretty sure you're not either,
are you?
Who cares if I'm not?
Hey, where I come from,
you can start drinking
as soon as you’re 16!
[Killua] I see.
Man. Look, I had no idea.
I’m just amazed you both got out alive.
Wow, I never realized
that the Phantom Troupe was so dangerous.
Oh! We actually used one of the tricks
that you taught us, Mr. Zepile.
-It really came in handy!
-Huh?
[crashing]
[Gon] If the exit is blocked...
[Killua] You’ve just gotta make your own!
[Zepile] I get it.
Even though I wasn’t there,
I’m glad I was able to help in some way.
[Zepile exhales]
I hadn't thought about it that way, but...
a little bit of con artistry
might actually go a long way
-against the Phantom Troupe.
-[Leorio] Right!
Forgery is the way to go!
You see, guys, I haven’t just
been drinking myself silly.
I’ve been learning a whole lot
from Zepile, here.
And tomorrow morning,
we'll hit up the auction.
You guys are coming too, right?
I'd like to, but I need to find Kurapika
and learn all about Nen.
Kurapika? So you got through to him?
Yep. But we’re waiting for him
to call us back.
Wait. You say you’re going to learn
about Nen from him?
-Yeah, that's right.
-Why?
He just learned about Nen
himself, didn't he?
Sure, but Kurapika managed to defeat
a member of the Phantom Troupe.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
He knows something about it we don’t.
He has to.
Like a strength that doesn’t need power
or even experience to make it work.
[Neon squealing]
Awesome! Thank you so much, Daddy!
[giggles] So pretty!
[Nostrade chuckles]
So, am I off the hook now?
[Neon] Uh huh! I forgive you!
Well, that’s certainly good to hear.
[Neon laughing]
Good work, all of you.
My daughter’s condition has improved
so we’ll be heading back to the hotel.
Tomorrow, we need to buy
that actor’s used tissue.
And that will be the end of the auction.
The day after tomorrow,
I’ll leave first thing in the morning.
However, I want you to accompany
my daughter while she shops.
[all groaning]
[Melody] Kurapika.
Don’t worry about the rest of the auction
and the shopping trip.
We’ll handle it ourselves.
You should get some rest, okay?
Yes, you’re right.
Thanks. I think I will.
[Basho] Is he really okay?
[dialing]
[Gon] Hello? Kurapika?
Yeah.
You said you wanted
to stop the Troupe, right?
Well, that won’t be necessary now.
The Spiders are dead.
[Gon gasps] What do you mean?
Kurapika?
[dial tone]
[Hisoka] Hmm. What a shame.
And here I was trying
to lift his spirits a little.
[Feitan]
The Mafia community was nothing special.
[Shalnark] We didn't even need Nobunaga!
[Nobunaga] Hey, shut up!
So, what'd he say?
That the Phantom Troupe's dead.
-They're what?
-You're kidding me!
[Gon] And then he hung up.
I guess I can’t find out any more…
[sighs]
[narrator] Kurapika is now drowning
in an indescribable emptiness.
[theme music playing]
-[Gon] Coming up, Gon...
-[Killua] And Killua's...
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I'm Gon!
-I'm Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we’ll introduce Kortopi,
a Troupe member!
Keep an eye out for Gallery Fake!
He touches something with his left hand
and conjures a copy with his right.
-I might be a fake too, you know?
-What?
[Gon] Next time:
"Fortunes Aren't Right?"
[Killua] My horoscope's terrible today.
[Gon] Hey! A Choco Robo on the ground!
[Killua] Lucky me!
So much for that horoscope!